[{"question": " tell him.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " tell him, tell him.", "answer": " just...please tell him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " shut up!", "answer": " tell me what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " look at you, you won't even look at him.", "answer": "  oh, come on tell me. i could use another reason why women won\u00b4t look at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " all right, all right, all right. last night, i had a dream that, uh, you and i, were...", "answer": " doing it on this table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " exellent dream score.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " why, why, why would you dream that?", "answer": " more importantly, was i any good?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " well, you were pretty damnedy good.", "answer": " interesting, cause in my dreams, i\u00b4m allways surprisingly inadequate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well, last night you seemed to know your way around the table.", "answer": " i love it, when we share.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " you\u00b4re okay there?", "answer": " i can\u00b4t belive you two had sex in her dream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hi rachel.", "answer": " get off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  uh, uh, gimme. can you see me operating a drill press?", "answer": " i don\u00b4t know. what are you wearing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " phoebs, why would you want to operate a drill press?", "answer": " just for some short-term-work. you know, until i get back some of my massage clients.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " pirates again?", "answer": " no, nothing like that. i was just...such a dummie. i taught this \"massage-yourself-at-home-workshop\". and they are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey, hey, chan. she could work for you.", "answer": "  thanks joey, that\u00b4s a good idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " what... i could, i could do it. what is it?", "answer": " well, my secretary is gonna be out for a couple of weeks. she is having one of her boobs redused. it\u00b4s a whole big boob story.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " i could be a secretary.", "answer": " well, you know phoebs. i don\u00b4t know if it\u00b4s your kinda thing, because it involves a lot of being normal. for a large portion of the day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " what are you playing with?", "answer": " oh, it\u00b4s my new beeper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " what the hell does a paleontologist need a beeper for?", "answer": " is it like for dinosaur emergencies. 'help, come quick, they\u00b4re still extinct.'", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " no, it\u00b4s for when carol goes into labor. she can get me wherever i am. i mean, all she has to do is to dial 55-jimbo.", "answer": " a cool phone number, and a possible name for the kid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " off to see young ethan?", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " how young is young ethan? young?", "answer": " he\u00b4s... our age.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " when we were?", "answer": " okay, he\u00b4s a senior in college.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " college?", "answer": " whoa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " and this manchild has no problem with how old you are?", "answer": " no, of course not. it\u00b4s not even an issue. cause i told him i was 22.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " oh, i can\u00b4t pass for 22?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " well, maybe 25-26.", "answer": " i am 26.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " can you hear that?", "answer": "  yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " see that\u00b4ll stop when you pick up the phone.", "answer": " oh. uh, i\u00b4m on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  mr. bing\u00b4s office. no i\u00b4m sorry, he\u00b4s in a meeting right now.", "answer": " i\u00b4m not in a meeting. i\u00b4m right... whoops.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " will he know what this is in reference to? and he has your number? all right, i\u00b4ll see that he gets the message. bye bye.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " ross says hi.", "answer": " ah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " this is so fun. all right, what do we do now?", "answer": " well, now, i actually have to get to work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " most likely.  okay, i\u00b4m gonna be out there.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " all right. bye bye.", "answer": " bye bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " whatcha doin\u00b4?", "answer": " ooh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " windows are clean, candels are lit. uh, belt\u00b4s to tight, gotta change the belt. did i turn the fish?  no, cause i made lasagne. am i out of control?", "answer": " just a touch. mon, i don\u00b4t understand. i mean, you\u00b4ve been dating this guy since like, what... his midterms? i mean, why all the sudden are you so... oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " could tonight be the night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i don\u00b4t know. look he\u00b4s a great guy and i love being with him but... you know. things happen, and they happen. you don\u00b4t plan these things.", "answer": " so, did you shave your legs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " aha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh, oh. oh, oh. oh this is it. oh my god it\u00b4s baby time. baby time.", "answer": " all right, relax, relax. just relax, just relax. be cool, be cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  yeah, hi, i was just beeped.  no, andr\u008f is not here.  third time today.  yes, i\u00b4m sure... no, sir. i don\u00b4t perform those kind of services.", "answer": " services? oh, services.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hey, hey. how was the first day?", "answer": " oh, exellent. everyone was so, so nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " see, it pays to know the man who wears my shoes.  me.", "answer": " no, i didn\u00b4t tell anybody that i knew you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " oh, because, you know... they don\u00b4t like you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i thought you knew that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " noho. why doesn\u00b4t they like me?", "answer": " everyone. except for uh... no everyone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " what are you talking about?", "answer": " don\u00b4t feel bad. you know they used to like you a lot. but then you got promoted, and, you know, now you\u00b4re like \"mr. boss man\". you know, mr. bing. mr. bing, \"boss man bing\".", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i can\u00b4t belive it.", "answer": " yeah, yeah. they even do you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " they do me?", "answer": " you know like... uh okay... uh... 'could that report be any later?'", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " i don\u00b4t sound like that.", "answer": " oh, oh chandler...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh... yeah, you do.", "answer": " 'the hills were alive with the sound of music.'", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " did not.", "answer": " i am telling you, up until i was, like nine, i thought that gunpoint was an actual place wher crimes happen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " how was that possible?", "answer": " well, think about it. it\u00b4s always on the news. 'a man is being held up, at gunpoint.' 'tourists are being terrorised, at gunpoint.' you know, i just kept thinking: why does people continue to go there? oh, ah. i should go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " unless--", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " uh, ah. unless you wanna stay over? i mean, i\u00b4m going to, so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " uuh, before we get into any staying-over-stuff, there is something you should know.", "answer": " okay, is this like 'i have an early class tomorrow' or 'i\u00b4m secretly married to a goat'?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " well it\u00b4s somewhere in between. you see, in a strictly technical sense, of course, i\u00b4m not uh..., well i, i mean i haven\u00b4t ever uh...", "answer": " ethan--", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " are you a virgin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " well, if that\u00b4s what you kids are calling it these days then, yes i am. i uh, i\u00b4ve kinda been waiting for the right person.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " you keep saying that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " listen, uh, you told me something that was really difficult for you. and i, i-i figured if you could be honest, then i can to.", "answer": " oh god, don\u00b4t tell me, i did it wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no no. nothing wrong about that.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " um, okay, here it goes. i\u00b4m not 22. i\u00b4m, i\u00b4m 25... and thirteen months.", "answer": " huh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " uh, listen um, as long as we\u00b4re telling stuff, uh, i have another one for you. i\u00b4m a little younger than i said.", "answer": " you\u00b4re not a senior?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh, i\u00b4m a senior... in high school.", "answer": " ok...ay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " what we did was wrong. oh god, i just had sex with somebody that wasn\u00b4t alive during the bicentennial.", "answer": " i just had sex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " ethan, focus. how could you not tell me?", "answer": " well, you never told me how old you were.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well, that\u00b4s different. my lie didn\u00b4t make one of us a felon in 48 states. what were you thinking?", "answer": " i wasn\u00b4t thinking. i was too busy fallin'--", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " --in love with you.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  sorry.", "answer": " well,fall out of it. you know, you shouldn\u00b4t even be here, it\u00b4s a school night. oh god, oh god. i\u00b4m like those women that you see with shiny guys like chad. i\u00b4m joan collins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  okay, andr\u008f should be there in like 45 minutes. all rightie, bye bye.  just easier that way.", "answer": " oh, come on. you told me about the last dream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " no, forget it.", "answer": " oh, why not. was i doing anything particularly... saucy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " all right, fine. um, you were not the only one there.  joey was there too.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " was there...uh, huh, huh, huh... andybody, anybody else there.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " you\u00b4re sure? nobody uh, handed out uh, mints or anything?", "answer": " no, it was just the three of us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " huh!", "answer": " so, tell me. was it like you and chandler, and then you and me, or you and me and chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " he, he, he. you know what?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " that is so sweet, you guys.   ross, rachel & phoebe: hey, mon.", "answer": " mon, ethan called again. mon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " ethan called again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " are you not seeing him anymore?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " no. you know, sometimes just things doesn\u00b4t work out.", "answer": " and this has nothing to do with the fact that he needs a note to get out of gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i, i didn\u00b4t say any... i sw... i did not say anything, i swear.", "answer": " listen, the next time you talk to him, can you ask him which one the strongest \"power ranger\" is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh, yeah.", "answer": " ha,ha, ha, oh my life is just so amusing. could we drop it now? joey, chandler & ross: sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " it\u00b4s morphin time!", "answer": " stegosaurus!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " ooh, oh, i\u00b4ve gotta go.  whoa, oh, head rush. one more, and then i have to go.  cool!", "answer": " where are you going?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " um, oh, i\u00b4ve got a birthday party, with some work people.", "answer": " work people? nobody told me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " no, i know. that\u00b4s a part of the whole, you know, them-not-liking-you-extravagance.", "answer": " you know, i don\u00b4t get this. a month aga, these people were my friends. you know, just because i\u00b4m in charge doesn\u00b4t mean i\u00b4m a different person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " well, then you should come tonight. you know, just hang out with them. let them see what a great guy you still are.", "answer": " you think i should?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " i really do, yeah.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i think last night was great. you know, the karaoke thing. tracy and i doing \"ebony and ivory\".", "answer": " you were great. but they still made fun of you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " you know, now you\u00b4re more like, you know like, \"mr. caring boss\", \"mr.\", you know, \"i\u00b4m one of you, boss\", \"mr., i wanna be your buddy, boss man bing\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " then, i don\u00b4t get it.", "answer": " well, you know what chandler? i think you\u00b4ve gotta face it. you\u00b4re like, the guy in the big office, you know. you\u00b4re the one that hires them, that fires them... they still say you\u00b4re a great boss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " they do?", "answer": " uh huh. but they\u00b4re not your friends anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i just wan\u00b4t to--", "answer": " no, but you can\u00b4t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " but i just wa--", "answer": " uh uh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " aren\u00b4t you gonna--", "answer": " oh, carol and i have a new system. if she punches in 911, it means she\u00b4s having a baby, otherwise i just ignore it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " what about andr\u008f?", "answer": " oh, welll this morning he got a call from who i think was our cousin nathan, and frankly, it was a little more than i needed to know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " that was gonna be my opener.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  hey, did you guys check out those new handdryers in the bathroom?", "answer": " i thought that was just a rumour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " true story.", "answer": " they\u00b4re here allready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " all right, look. i\u00b4ve gotta tell you something. i\u00b4m not 17. i only said so that you\u00b4d think i was cute and vunerable. i\u00b4m actually 30, i have a wife, i have a job, i\u00b4m your congressman. monica, this is ridiculous, we\u00b4re great together. we can talk , we make each other laugh, and the sex. oh, man, okay i have no frame of graft, but i thought that was great.", "answer": " it was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " then, what\u00b4s the problem?", "answer": " ethan, it\u00b4s um... it\u00b4s icky.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " icky? you\u00b4re actually gonna throw this away because it\u00b4s icky?", "answer": " this isn\u00b4t easy for me either. i wish things were different, i... if you were a few years older, or if i was a few years younger, or if we lived in biblical times, i would really--", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " are you\u00b4re hands still wet?", "answer": " uh, moist, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " uh, like, could these margaritas be any stronger?  hey, chandler.", "answer": " hello, mr. bing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " loved your \"stevie wonder\" last night.", "answer": " thanks. listen, about the weekly numbers, i\u00b4m gonna need them on my desk by nine o\u00b4clock.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " sure.", "answer": " no problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " you have to give \u00b4em something, you know. okay, now that was gerston, santos, and who\u00b4s the guy with the moustache?", "answer": " petrie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " ross?", "answer": " i\u00b4m here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " you are. well, um... we, we, we were just...", "answer": " what?  great, now i\u00b4m having a baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " ooh, ooh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i\u00b4m having... i\u00b4m having a baby.  i\u00b4m having a... where\u00b4s the phone? the phone?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " ross?", "answer": " i\u00b4m hurt. closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " hey ross, look what i\u00b4ve got going here.", "answer": " yeah, save it for the cab, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " what are you doing? we\u00b4re going to a hospital.", "answer": " what, so i can\u00b4t lokk nice? there might be doctors there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " joey, get out of the fridge.", "answer": " all right, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " for the ride.", "answer": " yeah, like in a cab--", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " save it.", "answer": " okay, hating this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " i can\u00b4t belive it, i\u00b4m gonna be an aunt. i\u00b4m gonna have like a nephew.", "answer": " that\u00b4s nice. get out let\u00b4s go, come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " here we go, here we go.", "answer": " rossy, rossy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s1/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}]